You are getting to be a big Charmer and have lots of imagination.
你会变成一个大魔法师  并且拥有丰富的想象力
I will let you help magic the eggs this year.
今年我会让你帮我给这些鸡蛋施魔法的
Really? Charmtastic! Whoo! Yeah!
真的吗  魔法神奇  喔哦  好耶
Remember, Hazel, the whole town is counting on you.
记着  黑尔兹  整个小镇都靠你呢
Sparksolutely.
保证完成任务
And you'll be sure to charm every single egg and have them ready for the Sparkle Bunny?
你一定要让每一个鸡蛋都充满魅力  准备好迎接闪闪发光的兔子了吗
Charmsitively.
神奇无比
-Because no eggs, no egg hunt, right?  -Right.
-因为没鸡蛋  就没寻彩蛋  对吧  -对
-You will not be sorry, mom.  -Okay, you better get crackin'.
-你不会后悔吧  妈妈  -好吧  你最好快点
Yah, I mean, get charming.
唔  我的意思是  变得更迷人
Whoo! Thanks, mom!
喔哦  谢谢你  妈妈